- 자, 한 장 집어
- 좋아
Pick a card.
All right. Now, memorize it.
이제 잘 기억해둬
-You got it?
-Oh, yes.
- 됐어?
- 그래
좋아, 이 거지?
Is that your card?
Yes.
맞다
-Hey, guys.
-Hi there!
- 안녕?
- 어서 와요
안녕
Guess what.
Ben is gonna be in a TV commercial.
놀라지 말아요, 우리 벤이
TV 광고에 나갈지도 몰라요
그게 무슨 소리예요?
What are you talking about?
아직 확실하진 않은데
It's not for sure, but...
공원에서 어떤 남자가 다가와서
벤이 너무 귀엽다고 하는 거야
...we met this guy in the park
who thought Ben was cute.
You know, which he is.
He gave us his card...
사실이 그렇지만
아무튼 그 남자가 명함을 주면서
자기 광고 오디션에 데려와 보래
...and told us to bring him
for this commercial he's auditioning.
This guy's the biggest commercial
casting director in town!
이 사람 광고 캐스팅에선
알아주는 거물이야
Ben takes one lousy walk
in the park and gets an audition?
겨우 공원 산책 한번 하고
오디션 제의를 받았다고?
I mean, way to go, Ben!
장하다, 벤
I've been in that park a million times
and no one's offered me an audition.
난 그 공원에 수백 번 다녀도
국물도 없더니만
우리도 놀랐다니까
벤 그네 태워주는데...
It's crazy. We were pushing
Ben on the swings
나도 갈 때마다 그네 타
I'm always on the swings!
What am I doing wrong?
내가 뭘 잘못했지?
That.
그거
The One Where Rachel Smokes
드디어 나 출근한다
행운을 빌어줘
-Gotta go. Wish me luck.
-Good luck.
잘해라
Since you work at Ralph Lauren,
can you get me some shirts?
이제 랄프 로렌 직원이니까
폴로셔츠 몇 벌 갖다 줄래?
I don't know if I'd feel comfortable
stealing on my very first day.
출근 첫날부터 회사물건
슬쩍하는 건 꺼림칙한데?
Unwilling to steal from work.
회사물건에 손대기 싫다...
Interesting.
희한하군
If anybody gets free stuff,
it's me.
설사 가져와도
그건 내 차지야
행운 안 빌어줄 거야?
Okay, guys, way to wish me luck.
- 행운을 빈다
- 잘될 거야
Go get 'em!
Let's discuss Rachel's birthday.
레이첼 생일에 어떻게 할까?
주말에 깜짝 파티 어때?
I say we throw
a surprise party this weekend.
But her birthday's
not for another month.
생일은 한 달이나 남았는데?
생일날 하는 게
무슨 깜짝 파티야?
If we throw her party on her birthday,
it's not a surprise.
좋은 생각 같다
Great! We can have a dinner party
and just invite her close friends.
가까운 친구들끼리
저녁이나 먹지 뭐
Ross! We're having
a surprise party for Rachel.
로스, 레이첼한테
깜짝 파티 열어줄 거다!
- 알았어!
- 초대 끝
Done.
Great. Wanna do it together?
- 나랑 같이 해볼래?
- 그럼 좋지
I'd love to do it together!
They're gonna do it together.
둘이 할 거래
That's my girlfriend.
- 얘는 내 여자친구야
- 그럼 이젠 상상도 못해?
So I gotta shut it down now?
I gotta go.
I'm picking up Ben...
난 이제 가봐야겠다
벤 데리고 오디션에 가야 돼
...and then we're off
to the big audition.
It's gonna be weird seeing some actor
pretending to be Ben's dad.
다른 사람이 벤 아빠로 나오면
기분이 좀 이상할 텐데
Weirder than seeing his two moms make out?
동거하는 엄마 둘보다 더?
Dad? There's a dad
in the commercial?
뭐, 아빠?
그 광고에 아빠도 나와?
그래, 아빠랑 아들이
수프를 맛있게 먹지
Yeah. The dad and Ben eat soup
and pretend to enjoy it.
그럼 나도 같이 가서
아빠 역을 지원해보자
Maybe I'll go with you
and audition as the dad.
Who better to play Ben's father
than his godfather?
아빠 역이라면 대부인
내가 해야 마땅하지
-You're not his godfather.
-What?
- 네가 무슨 대부냐?
- 뭐?
Are you kidding?
정말이야?
Of course I am.
물론 농담이지
-Okay, let's go, godfather.
-All right!
- 가자, 대부야
- 그래
야, 성공이다
나도 들어갔어
They're gonna let me audition!
- 정말? 잘됐다
- 그렇지?
Really? That's great!
One of the casting ladies
has actually seen me in a play.
담당자 중에 내 연극을
본 여자가 있더라고
그래서 그 여자만 피해 다녔지
So I steered clear of her.
And the other one, I know from....
또 한 명도 아는 여잔데...
뻔하잖아
Well, you know.
-That kid looks familiar.
-Oh, yeah.
저 애 어디서 봤는데
네, 광고에 굉장히
많이 나왔어요
He's done tons of commercials.
I've seen him in Sugar Smacks, PlayStation...
시리얼 광고는 물론
플레이스테이션
...and that one
for the phone company.
전화회사 광고도 했어
그것 때문에 나도
전화회사 바꿨잖아
He was so good, he convinced me
to switch phone companies.
Chandler was mad.
챈들러한테 맞아죽을 뻔했다
He's not gonna get this one.
Ben is way cuter than that kid.
이번엔 어림없어
벤이 훨씬 귀여우니까
I mean, look at him.
얘를 봐
어이구, 내 새끼...
That's great.
가관이다, 내가 벤 아빠로
뽑히면 좋을 텐데, 그치?
Wouldn't it be great
if I got to play Ben's dad?
넌 벤이랑 너무 안 닮았어
You look nothing like Ben.
너보단 많이 닮았다
I look more like him than you do.
I really don't know you
well enough for you to do that.
조이, 나랑 그 정도로
친한 사이 아니잖아요?
So it's down to these two.
Nancy, I know you like this one.
결국 두 개로 좁혀졌네
낸시는 이게 맘에 들고
나도 그렇거든
I think I agree.
Rachel, what do you think?
레이첼 생각은 어때?
Well, that one is pretty...
그것도 괜찮지만
전 이 옷감이 너무 좋아요
...but I just love this fabric.
Sorry.
미안해요
미안할 거 없어
의견제시도 업무의 일환이야
Don't be. Part of your job
is to give your opinions.
그 공은 내 차지지만
농담이야
Then I take credit for them.
I'm kidding!
She is kidding. But don't ever
disagree with her again.
농담하신 거예요
하지만 다시는 부장님
의견에 반대하지 말아요
Okay, now I'm kidding!
이번엔 내가 농담한 건데
What a fun office.
분위기 참 화기애매하네요
I don't know which one.
But I do know I need a cigarette.
결정을 못 내리겠네
담배 한 대 피워야겠어
Let's take a break, go outside
and sort this out when we return.
어때, 잠깐 바람 쐬고
들어와서 다시 얘기하지
레이첼?
- 네?
- 담배 피워?
-You smoke?
-No.
아뇨, 아빠가 의사신데
너무 끔직한 얘기를 들어서...
My dad's a doctor. And he would
always tell me horror stories....
유령이랑 도깨비들 얘긴데
About ghosts and goblins...
공주의 흡연권을 전적으로
지지하는 내용이었죠
...who totally supported
the princess' right to smoke.
And then they came back from smoking
and they'd made all of the decisions.
밖에서 담배 피우면서
둘이 결정을 다 내렸더라고
-That's not fair.
-I know.
- 너무한다
- 누가 아니래
그 역겨운 걸 안 피운다고
이런 꼴을 당해야 돼?
It's like I'm being punished for not having
this disgusting, poisonous habit.
그 맛 죽이지
Yeah, it is the best.
What if this keeps happening?
계속 이렇게 담배 피우면서
결정을 다 내리면 어떡하지?
They'll be smoking,
making the decisions...
...and I'll be up in my office
breathing in my stupid clean air.
난 혼자 사무실에 멀뚱히 앉아
거지같은 맑은 공기나 마셔?
And when Kim wants
to promote one of us...
이러다 승진 기회가 나면
부장이 누굴 뽑겠니
...who do you think she'll pick?
Me or Smokey Smokerson?
날까, 그 골초계집일까?
We used to have
a smoking area at work.
우리 직장엔
흡연구역이 있었는데
거기 큰 화분에 재가 많아서
우린 거기다 담배를 껐거든
It was great. There was this
big flowerpot with dirt in it.
We used to put our cigarettes out in it.
One of the old-timers told me
there used to be a little tree in there.
고참 말로는
거기 나무가 있었대
You can go down there and not smoke.
Say you want some fresh air.
따라 나가서 담배는 피우지 말고
신선한 공기 마시러 나왔다고 해
I could do that.
그래야겠다
Or you could do
the easy thing and smoke.
골머리 썩이지 말고
그냥 피우든가
You gotta take long, deep drags.
길게 빨아들이는 한 모금
Wow, I still don't have
my lung capacity back yet.
아직 폐가 회복이 안 됐네
- 얘들아
- 어서 와
Rach, do you wanna go get coffee?
- 레이첼, 커피 마시러 갈래?
- 그거 좋지
-I would love to.
-Oh, good.
- 잘됐다
- 나도 갈래
I'm gonna go too.
Oh, good.
잘됐다
Oh, I changed my mind.
난 가기 싫어졌다
Let's talk about the party.
I have so many ideas.
그럼 파티 얘기를 해볼까?
아이디어가 마구 넘친다
Me too!
- 나도!
- 어디 보자...
Oh, look at that.
어, 멋지다
This is a little sketch
of the cake. See?
케이크를 그려봤어
- 잘했다
- 자, 이걸 봐
Some sample menus.
이건 샘플 메뉴...
I thought we'd start with
a Tuscan-style finger food.
토스카나 스타일의
핑거푸드로 시작하려고
And for music, here's an
alphabetized list of all of my CDs.
그리고 음악, 내 CD를
알파벳순으로 정리한 거야
I've highlighted the ones
that'll go with the food.
요리랑 잘 어울리는 건
밑줄 쫙 그어뒀어
-What about the intimate dinner party?
-We're not doing that.
- 조촐한 파티라면서
- 그런 게 어딨어!
됐지? 그리고...
알았어, 너 혼자 다해라
같이 하자더니 수고 많았다
Looks like you took care of
everything. Thanks a lot, cohost.
Wait a minute. There's plenty
of things for you to do.
왜 그래?
나 혼자 다하다니
네가 할 일도 많아
그래? 어떤 거?
Like what?
Cups.
컵
You're giving me cups?
컵?
나더러 컵을 맡으라고?
And ice.
그리고 얼음
Cups and ice? I get to be
in charge of cups and ice?
컵이랑 얼음?
내가 컵과 얼음 담당이야?
All right.
알았어
Fine. I will be
in charge of cups and ice.
좋아, 컵과 얼음은
내가 책임지겠어
-I can get ice at the restaurant
-I got it!
- 참, 얼음은 우리 식당에서...
- 싫어, 내가 할래
- 나 왔다
- 어서 와
오디션은 어땠어?
-How did the audition go?
-Not so good.
망쳤다
잠깐...
조이 흉내내는 거지?
Wait a minute.
Are you doing Joey's:
"The audition didn't go so well....
Yeah, it did"?
'나 오디션 망쳤다'
'망치긴 왜 망쳐! '
Yeah, I am!
맞아, 그거야!
-Yeah, Ben got a second audition.
-That's great!
- 1차 합격이야
- 잘됐다
I had to teach Ross my bit because
I actually didn't get a callback.
로스한테 내 수법 알려줬어
난 미끄러졌거든
You got a callback too, didn't you?
너도 붙었다, 그치?
Yeah, I did!
그래, 맞아!
레이첼, 여긴 왜 나왔어?
What are you doing out here?
혼자 있으려니 심심해서
그냥 나와봤어요
It got kind of lonely up there,
so I thought I would come out here...
...and get some fresh air.
신선한 공기나 마실까 하고
We're discussing the fall collection.
낸시랑 가을 컬렉션
얘기를 하고 있었어
Oh, great.
- 그래요?
- 그래서 말인데, 우리...
Anyway, we really
-Sorry. We're smoking all over you.
-That's okay.
미안해, 연기가 다
자기한테 가네
- 미안해요
- 아니, 괜찮아요
아냐, 우리가 옮길게
자긴 그냥 있어
We'll move. You stay there.
I sent the designs to Ralph.
He was excited about it.
랄프한테 그 디자인 보냈더니
굉장히 좋아하더라고요
그거 잘됐다
역시 자기가 최고야
That's great!
You are the best!
Excuse me.
Can I bum one of those?
한 대만 빌려주실래요?
Actually, this one's....
아니, 그거요...
뭐죠? 뭐가 그렇게
재미있어요?
What's so funny over here?
담배 안 피우잖아요
I thought you didn't smoke.
You know, I thought you guys
meant marijuana cigarettes.
전 그게 마리화나인 줄 알고
You know what I mean?
Doobies?
아시죠? 맛 가는 대마초
속으로 꽤 놀랐어요
'어쩜 이럴 수가! '
Actually, I thought to myself,
"Those guys are crazy!"
But no, I smoke the
regular ones all the time.
하지만 실은 저도 골초예요
We get high.
대마초도 하는데?
Me too.
저두요
I'm kidding.
농담이야
Me too.
저두요
Oh, God! This is so nerve-racking.
How do you do this?
조마조마해서 미치겠다
넌 이런 걸 어떻게 견디니?
Fortunately, I don't get
many callbacks, so....
다행히 2차까지 가는
경우는 아주 드물거든
Is it a good sign that
they asked us to wait?
오디션 끝나고 남으라는 게
좋은 뜻일까요?
Who knows?
난들 아나요
좋아요, 최종후보자는
We have narrowed it down
to Raymond, Ben, Kyle...
레이먼드, 벤, 카일
그리고 조이입니다
...and Joey.
The rest of you, thank you.
나머지는 수고 많으셨어요
Yes! I knew it!
아싸! 될 줄 알았어!
Bye-bye.
잘 가요
So long.
안녕
Later.
또 봅시다
난 이 사람 부인 아니에요
전남편이라구요
I'm not married to him anymore.
He's my ex-husband. I'm totally gay!
난 동성애자예요
내가 정말 벤의 아빠 역을
맡게 될지도 모르겠다
This is great!
I might get to play Ben's dad.
Actually, that can't happen.
그런 일은 없을 거예요
외모가 너무 달라서
Because you have
such different looks...
당신은 레이먼드와 짝이고
벤은 카일과 짝이에요
...we're putting you with Raymond
and Kyle with Ben.
이 두 사람이 되든지
이 두 사람이 되는 거죠
So it'll either be
you two or you two.
이런...
-This is gonna be kind of weird.
-Yeah, it is.
일이 묘하게 꼬이네
그러게
Yeah. It's gonna be weird.
네, 정말 그렇군요
No. We're like best friends.
That's why it's weird.
아뇨, 저희 둘은 친구거든요
그래서 꼬였다고 한 거예요
저런, 난 또 얘기나
하자는 줄 알았네
I thought we were just talking.
If Ben gets this commercial, do you
think you can get me some free soup?
벤이 광고에 출연하게 되면
공짜 수프 좀 갖다 줄 수 있냐?
Chandler, a can of soup is like 60 cents.
수프 한 깡통에
60센트밖에 안 해
Yeah, okay, but I have been supporting
a 29-year-old ltalian for five years.
하지만 난 29세의 이태리
사람을 5년이나 후원했어
- 얘들아
- 그래
Is it okay if I leave this here
till Rachel's birthday party?
레이첼 생일파티 때까지
이거 여기 좀 둬도 될까?
-Sure. What's in them?
-Cups.
그래, 뭔데?
컵이야
Good, because we got Rachel
800 gallons of water.
잘됐다, 우린 레이첼한테
물 800갤런 선물할 건데
무슨 컵이 그리 많아?
That's a lot of cups.
내가 컵이랑 얼음 담당이거든
I'm in charge of cups and ice.
And Monica's gonna rue the day
she put me in charge of cups and ice.
모니카는 나한테 이걸 맡긴 거
가슴 치며 후회하게 될 거야
You know, I rued the day once.
Didn't get a whole lot else done.
나도 가슴 치며 후회해봤는데
달라지는 건 하나도 없더라
Okay, time to bring up
the rest of the cups.
나머지 컵도 가져와야겠다
- 안녕, 조이
- 그래, 피비
Ross, I'm glad you're here.
로스, 마침 있었구나
나랑 얘기 좀 하자
-I want to talk to you.
-What's up?
뭔데?
I've been thinking about this
commercial thing. Me against Ben.
이번 일 많이 생각해봤는데
벤하고 경쟁한다는 게
아무래도 마음에 걸려
The two of us competing.
That can't lead to anything good.
누구한테도 이로울 게 없어
I think I'm just gonna step aside.
I'll tell them that I won't audition.
그래서 내가 물러서기로 했다
오디션 안 한다고 연락할 거야
그런 생각까지 했구나
정말 고맙다
Joey, that's great.
Thanks, man.
That's it?
그게 다야?
그냥 그러고 말아?
내 밥줄이 걸린 일이야
You're gonna let me do this?
It's my career we're talking about!
But you just
- 하지만 네가 방금...
- 그럼 네가 포기할 줄 알았지
I just said that
so you wouldn't let Ben do it.
하나가 양보해야 한다면
그건 바로 벤이야
If anyone should step aside,
it should be Ben.
-What?
-Chandler, tell him!
- 뭐?
- 챈들러, 한마디 해
Well, let me get the door first.
난 문부터 열어주고
Hi, no one!
어서 와라, 허깨비야
Why should Ben step aside?
왜 벤이 양보해야 하는데?
애초부터 벤의 오디션이었어
It was his audition in the
first place. You tagged along.
넌 그냥 따라온 거잖아
벤의 곁가지 아빠로
You're like the tagalong dad!
At least I care about his feelings.
벤을 생각해서 이러는 거야
What?
뭐라구요?
You know how hard it'll be on him
when he doesn't get it?
떨어지면 얼마나 실망이
클지 생각이나 해봤어?
And why wouldn't he get it?
- 왜 떨어지는데?
- 정신 차려
Come on!
Have you seen what my kid can do?
우리 아들 하는 거 못 봤어?
걘 전화도 걸 줄 알고
토르티야 칩도 먹고
He dials phones,
he eats tortilla chips.
He plays soccer
with the cartoon tiger!
만화 호랑이랑 축구도 해
Are you saying your kid eats soup
better than my kid?
네 아들이 내 아들보다
수프를 더 잘 먹는다고?
네 아들한테 숟가락 줘봐라
You just give him a spoon, baby.
Oh, yeah? I guess we'll see!
그래? 두고 보자
좋지, 이 광고는
나랑 우리 미치 거야
This commercial belongs
to me and Mitch!
-Your kid's name is Raymond!
-Yeah? So is yours!
- 그 녀석 이름은 레이먼드다
- 그래, 너 잘났다
-How did work go?
-lt was great.
회사 일은 어때?
아주 좋아, 너희가 시킨 대로
나도 따라 나가서 얘길 했지
I went down there like you said.
And we talked business.
내 의견을 다 받아들이더라
And Kim took my opinions.
You stink!
냄새난다
-Thanks.
-No, I'm serious.
- 고맙다
- 아니, 진짜야
거기서 담배연기가 뱄을 거야
이게 바로 성공의 냄새란다
That's because I went down there
and they were smoking.
This is actually the smell of success.
But there's something different
그 냄새가 아닌데...
Oh, my God! You smoked!
맙소사, 너 피웠구나
I did not.
아냐
안 피우긴, 저 행복하면서도
메스꺼운 표정, 분명 피웠어
Yes, you did. You look
happy and sick. You smoked!
All right, fine! But I had to.
I had to do it for my career.
그래, 하지만 일을 위해선
어쩔 수 없었어
I wish I had to smoke for my career.
나도 일 때문에
피워봤음 좋겠다
But it's so gross!
- 너무 끔찍하다
- 그렇게 나쁘진 않아
It's not that bad, you know?
Yeah, my tongue feels a little fuzzy
and my fingers sort of smell.
그래, 혀가 좀 얼얼하고
손가락에서 냄새는 조금 나지
I actually feel like I could throw up.
실은 나 토할 것 같아
-Can you hear yourself?
-I know. I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
- 정신은 있어?
- 그래, 미안하다
몽롱해, 반 갑을 피웠더니
손이 떨리고 알딸딸한 게
I'm not myself.
I smoked like half a pack.
I feel a little shaky and a little weird.
But you gotta push past this, okay?
Because it's about to get so good.
그 순간을 견뎌야 돼
고비만 넘으면 천국이야
챈들러
You smell so smoky,
I gotta get up.
냄새가 너무 심해서
못 앉아있겠다
I'm not kidding.
진짜야
I think you smell great.
이게 무슨 향기냐
So we're decided.
No on plaid, yes on pink.
그럼 격자무늬 빼고
분홍색으로 결정한 거야
Absolutely.
좋아요
I'm so onboard.
지당하신 말씀
-Didn't you just light that?
-Yeah.
- 방금 불붙였잖아?
- 네
But you know what?
요즘 끊으려고 노력 중이거든요
I'm just really, really
trying to cut back, you know.
Good luck, Rach.
- 될 진 모르지만
- 그러게
I've been thinking about quitting.
저도 끊어야겠다는
생각은 하고 있어요
말도 마, 일요일 밤마다 끊자고
했다가 월요일 아침만 되면...
Every Sunday night,
I tell myself I'm quitting.
Every Monday morning, it's like:
Tell me about it.
그러게 말이에요
We'll just quit.
Let's all quit!
그럼 끊어요
같이 끊는 거예요
It sounds appealing.
- 말은 쉽지
- 전 못해요
-I never could do it.
-But you could. Absolutely.
끊을 수 있어요
서로 도우면 돼요
We can help each other.
We could get those patches.
금연패치도 있잖아요
패치 시스터즈 어때요?
We could be like the Patch Sisters.
끊긴 끊어야 하는데...
좋아, 끊자
You know, we really should quit.
Okay, let's quit!
네, 좋아요
이리 내놔요
Great! Give me those cigs.
Come on!
자, 됐어요
에잇, 죽어라
Give it! Out. Done. Quit.
My late husband gave me that lighter.
죽은 남편이 선물한 라이터야
I'm not kidding.
농담 아냐
Okay, then.
알았어요
Mmm...soup.
음, 수프...
음... 수프!
음! 수프
Would you mind watching Ben for me
while I use the ladies' room?
로스가 곧 오니까 화장실
다녀올 동안 벤 좀 봐줘요
-No problem.
-Thanks.
- 그러죠 뭐
- 고마워요
음, 수프...
안녕, 벤?
So you want to be an actor?
I gotta tell you, it's no picnic.
너 배우 될래?
아저씨가 말하는데
이건 장난이 아냐
There's tons of rejection.
No stability.
허구헌날 퇴짜 맞고
얼마나 불안한 직업인데
I mean, one day,
you're Dr. Drake Ramoray.
어느 날은 드레이크
라모레 박사였다가
The next day, you're eating
ketchup out of the bottle.
다음날 손가락 빠는 수가 있지
힘든 바닥이야, 물론
아무 때나 일어나도 되고
It's a tough life. I mean, sure,
you can get up whenever you want...
...watch TV all day...
종일 TV 보고
...meet tons of women in acting class....
연기학교에는
여자들이 깔렸지
Oh, who am I kidding. I can't
talk you out of this. It's a great life.
지금 내가 제정신이냐?
이렇게 멋진 직업을 두고
-Joey.
-Ross.
조이
로스
Ben.
벤
I mean, Ben. Ben.
아니, 우리 벤이지
자, 레이먼드와 조이
들어오세요
Raymond, Joey, you're up.
좋아요, 그럼 이제...
So here's what....
Are you sure that I haven't seen you
somewhere before?
정말 우리 어디서
만난 적 없어요?
No, I haven't been in any plays.
아뇨, 그럴 리가 있나요
자, 그럼 시작합시다
준비되는 대로
All right, let's try one.
Whenever you guys are ready.
Is there a problem?
왜 그러죠?
Well, this is noodle soup.
And I've been working with tomato.
이건 누들 수프군요
전 토마토 수프로 연습했는데
하지만 괜찮아요
문제없습니다
But that's okay. No problem.
음, 누들 수프
Mmm...noodle soup.
You know, that's fine.
But the line is, "Mmm...soup."
그것도 괜찮지만
대사는 '음, 수프'예요
-What'd I say?
-"Mmm...noodle soup."
제가 뭐라고 했죠?
'음, 누들 수프'
How's that different?
뭐가 다른데요?
오! 알겠습니다
All right. Let's try one.
- 됐죠? 갑시다
- 네
Mmm...
음, 누들 수프
...noodle soup.
- 좋아요, 한 번 더 하죠
- 네
Let's do it again.
Mmm...soup.
음... 수프
I mean, noodle soup.
I mean, soup!
아니, 누들 수프
아니, 수프
Come on!
뭐 하세요!
You know what?
We need to move on.
됐어요, 그만하세요
No, I could do it one more time.
한 번만 더 해볼게요
보세요
Look.
음... 누들 수프
우라질!
Mmm...noodle soup.
Damn it!
So I think that if we get these samples
into the magazine by Monday, we'll be fine.
이 샘플은 월요일까지만
잡지사로 보내면 될 거예요
좋아
Sounds good.
So, Rach, how you doing?
- 레이첼, 기분은 어때?
- 너무 좋아요
-I'm great!
-No, with the not-smoking thing.
아니, 금연 말이야
Kill me now.
진짜 죽을 맛이에요
제 말 들어보세요
Let me tell you something,
I ate 40 Mallomars today.
오늘 초콜릿을 40개나 먹고
온몸에 패치를 붙이고
I mean, I have patches
all over my body, you know?
- 이틀이나 잠을 설쳤어요
- 어제 끊었잖아
-I mean, I haven't slept in two days.
-We quit yesterday.
That's counting today.
오늘까지 쳐서
But anyway, so these samples, I think
- 어쨌든 이 샘플은 말씀드렸듯...
- 내 정신 좀 봐
Oh, my God!
I'm so sorry, I forgot. I have to go
to the mailroom and mail some proofs.
죄송해요, 깜빡했어요
우편물 보낼 게 좀 있는데
Go ahead. Rachel and I will just sit here
and keep brainstorming.
어서 다녀와, 난 레이첼
생각을 좀 더 들어봐야겠어
Also, Vogue called.
And they were wondering
- 또 보그 쪽에서는...
- 그러고 보니 좀 시장하네
You know what? I'm a little hungry. I'm just
gonna run down to the vending machines.
- 간단하게 요기나 해야겠어
- 그러세요
All right.
이런
Busted!
들켰네
Come on! What are you doing?
I thought we were the Patch Sisters.
지금 뭐하시는 거예요?
우린 패치 시스터즈잖아요
That didn't work out.
전혀 효과가 없더군
Wait a minute.
What about all we've talked about?
그 얘기 벌써 잊었어요?
이 역겨운 장소, 추한 사람들
You know, the disgusting place,
the ugly people.
Hey, how you doing?
아저씨도 오셨네?
레이첼, 노력했지만
너무 힘들어
We tried to quit.
But it was too hard.
If you started smoking again,
you could have at least told me.
다시 피울 거면 저한테
얘기는 해주셨어야죠
Give me one.
What are we talking about?
자, 한 대 주세요
까짓 거 뭐
안 돼, 자긴 잘하고 있어
포기하지 마
Don't you give up.
That's why we didn't tell you,
and we won't drag you down.
이래서 숨긴 거야
자기까지 끌어내리긴 싫어
아뇨, 끌어내려 주세요
Wait. No, no.
Drag me down.
Forget it. We're so proud
of how well you're doing.
안 돼, 레이첼
우린 자기가 자랑스러워
여기서 포기하면 곤란하지
I won't let you blow it.
If I catch you, you're fired.
자긴 피우다 들키면 해고야
그러니까 어서 들어가
Go on, get out of here.
I don't want you breathing this stuff.
- 연기 들이키지 말고
- 알았어요
So, okay. You'll come with me
on the Paris trip?
그건 그렇고 이번에
나랑 파리에 가는 거지?
Oh, man!
내가 미쳐
Check it out.
Cup hat, cup banner...
잘 봐
컵 모자, 컵 장식
컵 샹들리에, 원자재는 모두...
...cup chandelier, and the thing
that started it all: the cup!
컵이야
그 컵 정말 대단한데?
Great job with the cups.
Why don't you just go out with her?
아예 피비랑 사귀어라
Did you notice the ice? Look!
얼음도 봤니?
봐, 없는 게 없어
We have it all. We have crushed,
cubed and dry. Watch.
얼음가루, 얼음큐브
드라이아이스까지, 봐
Mystical.
신비롭지?
챈들러
내 요리엔 손도 안 대고
다들 피비 얼음과자만 먹어
No one's eating my food.
They're eating her snow cones!
There are snow cones?
얼음과자도 있어?
얼음과자? 으엑!
-Go, go!
-Thank you.
- 됐어, 가서 먹어
- 감사합니다
피비?
-You really did do a nice job.
-Thank you...
정말 잘했다
고맙다, 당연한 얘길 해줘서
...for stating the obvious.
I deserve that.
할말 없다
I just want you to know that if we ever
cohost a party together again...
다음에도 같이 할 기회가
생긴다면 네 결정을 따를게
-...you can do whatever you want.
-Joey's got a birthday coming up.
- 곧 조이 생일이거든
- 정말? 넌 뭐할 건데?
-Really? What do you wanna do?
-Okay, I'd like to be in charge of beer.
- 좋아, 난 맥주를 맡을게
- 그럼 내 일은 없잖아
Well, then there's nothing left for me.
-Look, look!
-Surprise!
- 왔다! 왔어!
- 놀랐지!
뭐야?
내 생일은 한 달이나 남았는데
What? My birthday is not
for another month.
That's the surprise.
그러니까 깜짝 파티지
Oh, my God, you guys!
This is so great! It's so unexpected.
세상에, 너무 근사하다
이래도 되는 거니?
I mean, Chandler's birthday
is even before mine.
챈들러 생일이 더 빠른데
Surprise!
놀랐지!
와, 정말 멋지다
이 컵 좀 봐
This is so great!
Look at all these...
...cups.
This is so weird.
분위기 참 야릇하다
I was in charge of cups.
내가 컵 담당이야
그렇게 야릇하진 않아
Oh, okay. Not so weird.
-Chandler, what are you doing?
-Nothing.
챈들러, 뭐해?
아냐
-What's in your hand?
-Money. I'm stealing all the money.
- 손에 든 건 뭐야
- 돈! 돈 훔치고 있어
Chandler.
챈들러
But just one, okay? Because nobody
knows when my birthday is.
딱 한 병만, 아무도
내 생일 모르잖아
Let me make this clear to you, okay?
확실히 해두자
그거야, 이거야?
It's either that...
...or this.
They were menthol.
박하향인데...
- 조이
- 그래
Listen, man. I'm sorry
the audition didn't go well.
저기...
오디션 망친 거 유감이다
Yeah, right.
좋아하시네
No, really. I am, Joey.
I feel bad.
진심이야
나도 속상해
Look, Ross.
You don't have to, okay?
이봐, 로스
그럴 필요 없어
It's not your fault I suck.
그게 왜 네 잘못이냐?
배우라는 놈 대사가
'음, 누들 수프'
What kind of an actor can't even say,
"Mmm...noodle soup"?
You know what? Maybe you didn't
mess up your audition because you suck.
오디션에서 떨어진 건
실력 때문이 아닐 거야
Maybe you messed up because
you care more about your godson.
자기 경력보다는 대부로서
벤을 더 사랑한다는 뜻이겠지
What do you mean?
무슨 소리야?
I think, subconsciously
- 그러니까 무의식적으로....
- 어허, 쉬운 말로
You lost me.
I think, on some level,
you sabotaged...
자기도 모르게 스스로
오디션을 망쳤단 얘기야
...your own audition
so Ben would get the part.
벤을 밀어주려고
Your way sounds
a lot better than mine.
그편이 훨씬 듣기 좋네
맞아
It's not that I'm a bad actor.
- 그래, 내가 왜 형편없어
- 아무렴
No, it's just that I care
so damn much about little Ben...
다시 말해서...
난 벤을 열라 아끼니까
...that it was more important
for me to see him succeed.
- 벤의 성공이 더 중요한 거야
- 바로 그거야
-There you go. Thank you.
-Thank you.
- 고마워
- 내가 고맙지
-So did he get it?
-No.
- 그래서 벤이 뽑혔냐?
- 아니
그럼 그렇지
What are you gonna do?
Is Rachel Green here?
I'm meeting her for lunch.
실례합니다, 레이첼 그린과
점심약속이 있는데
이제 여기 안 내려와요
10층으로 가보세요
She doesn't come down anymore.
You'll find her on 10.
알겠습니다
Okay, great.
So we talked
about the presentation.
어제 프레젠테이션
얘기를 했는데
He wondered if one person
would be enough.
이번 출장에 한 명만
데려갈 거냐고 묻길래
And I said, "Yeah, absolutely."
한 명이면 충분하다고 했어
I'll catch you guys later.
그럼 나중에 뵙죠